upspring.com 2012-01-01

# Upspring - Privacy Policy

### **Upspring's Privacy Policy**

* * *

Upspring ("we" or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit Upspring.com (collectively, the "Site") without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. By using this Site you agree to be bound by the policy set forth herein.

We may make changes to the Site or policies and conditions that govern the use of the Site at any time. We encourage you to review the policies periodically for any updates or changes.

Any use of the web site is at sole risk of the user. Your continued access or use of the Site shall be deemed your acceptance of these changes and the reasonableness of these standards for notice of changes. 

>   
> 
>   1. **Accuracy**
> 
> We do our best to maintain the accuracy of information you supply us.
> 
>   
> 
>   2. **Protecting Your Privacy**
> 
> • Your account information is password protected. Please help us by keeping your password safe. We do not publish your account information or share it with other individuals or organizations.
> 
> • Be aware that when you share your content and professional profile information, including age, gender, and contact information, with ‘everyone' you voluntarily display or distribute personal information, and that information shall be made available to the public and can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties over which Upspring is not responsible. Please review our Terms of Use before using our Site.
> 
> • We do not knowingly rent or sell your information to any third parties without your consent.
> 
>   
> 
>   3. **Information We Collect**
> 
> When you sign up for an account, we ask you to provide personal information about you by filling out and submitting a member profile. We ask for name, username, zip code, local time zone, email address, and password in order to create an account. Like all passwords, your password should be one that only you will know. You acknowledge that some of this information, including your name and email address is personal to you, and by creating an account on Upspring, you allow us to identify you. Additionally, some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on Upspring, including on your profile page, and in search results. 
> 
>   
> 
>   4. **Sharing information on Upspring**
> 
> This section explains how your information is shared on Upspring. We recommend that you check your privacy settings before sharing information on Upspring.
> 
> Upspring helps you connect and manage your professional and business community networks. We give you the opportunity to share your profile photo (“your avatar”) so others can identify and connect with you. You acknowledge that your name and profile photo do not have privacy settings. If you are uncomfortable with sharing your profile photo, you should not add one, and if you have added one, you should delete it. 
> 
> As a user, you may provide additional information about you, including your professional information, experiences, educational background, personal information, and contacts information. The additional information you provide is designed to help you get more benefits from Upspring, while enabling you to connect and build your professional network. By default, your personal and contact information is set to “Only Me” in your Privacy Settings, and therefore, is not visible to the public or your connections on Upspring. Other additional information, including basic information, professional summary, experiences, educational, and additional information section, is set to “Only My Connections”, allowing only the individuals you're connected with on Upspring with to view. We recommend that you always consider your privacy settings before sharing information on Upspring. 
> 
> If you choose to use our invitation service to recommend and invite your friends or contacts to join Upspring, we will ask for your friends' or contacts' name and email address. Upspring will send a one-time email to each individual you invite to join Upspring. You understand that you should not invite anyone you do not know or trust to connect with you. 
> 
> Additionally, Upspring notifies you via email whenever you receive new invitations, your invitations are accepted or denied, you receive new messages, you receive new questions, your questions have been answered, and you receive new comments on your Tell messages. You may opt out of receiving any notification email by changing your settings in the Notifications section. 
> 
> Occasionally, we may, for example, use your email address to send administrative emails and alerts to you concerning changes to our User Agreement or other important policy in which may affect your membership at Upspring.com. You may not opt-out of any such administrative emails. 
> 
>   
> 
>   5. **Security**
> 
> We will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we collect from you. Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.
> 
>   
> 
>   6. **External Links**
> 
> Upspring has links to other Web sites. Upspring is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.
> 
> Upspring welcomes links to our web site. Web site owners are free to establish a hypertext link to this site provided that we are not required to pay any sponsorship fees.
> 
> If at anytime our policy ever changes, we will post it in this page so that you will always understand how we use, collect and disclose your personal information.
> 
> 

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please send us an email to info at [upspring.com](http://www.upspring.com/ "http://www.upspring.com"). You may also write to us at:

Privacy 

### Upspring

P.O. Box 360638  
Milpitas, CA 95036-0638

Version BBP002 effective January 18, 2011
